把激光发射器打下来！把它打下来！
- Chookity? Chookity! - Shoot the laser. Shoot the laser!
月饼此时想说的是...
Gary: What Mooncak is trying to say here is...
从上一集的《终空》里我们得知
Previously on "Final Space"...
长久以来  阿瓦卡多一直
Avocato's been trying to save his son, Little Cato,
想救出他的儿子  也就是
for a long freakin' time,
被总司令囚禁起来的小卡多  我的天哪
who the Lord Commander has locked away. Oh, crap!
盖瑞曾经发誓过
Gary swore that he wouldn't rest
不安全救回小卡多  就绝不罢休
until Little Cato was back home safe,
而盖瑞  从来不食言
and Gary always keeps his word.
盖瑞  你还有4分钟氧气可用
Four minutes of oxygen left, Gary.
阿瓦卡多  是时候现身把我救出来了
Avocato, now would be the time to appear and scoop me up.
他不会来的  盖瑞
He's not coming, Gary.
恐怕没人会来
I'm afraid no one is.
HUE  有没有可能我其实是个不死族？
H.U.E., what are my chances that I'm secretly an immortal?
就像宙斯  赫拉克勒斯  或者八爪大恐龙一样？
Like Zeus, Hercules, or Octoprime Rex?
没有这个可能
There is no chance.
我觉得八爪大恐龙还是有可能的
I think there's a chance I got an Octoprime Rex thing going on.
而且很有可能
Big time.
完全没有这个可能
You have absolutely no chance
因为八爪大恐龙是你自己编出来的
because Octoprime Rex is completely fabricated by you.
那如果我们讨论一下
If we're talking percentages
我变成八面强化霸王龙的可能性
of me becoming an eight-sided enhanced T-Rex,
你觉得有多大可能？
what are the odds?
百分之零
Zero percent.
所以我算是死透了
So death it is.
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 专访听译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Chapter Six
终空  第一季第六集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
HUE 你能接个线吗
H.U.E., can you patch this in?
正在进行
H.U.E.: Transferring.
爸 这是我的坐标
Dad, these are my coordinates.
快来找我  我的意思是  等你有空的时候
Come find me. I mean, at your leisure,
不过还是希望你能快点
but like, for me preferably fast. That'd be great.
那是你的儿子吗
Is that your son?
- 是  - 看起来蛮健康的
- Yes. - He looks healthy.
我的意思是  呃  看起来
I mean, look, yeah, it looks like ... it looks like
你把他抚养得很好
you did a pretty good job raising the boy.
呃  很明显  他在按时洗澡
I mean, it's obvious he's been bathing.
我发现坐标位于11区的乌德里克斯星系
I've traced the coordinates to the Udrex System in Sector 11.
HUE  设置一下航线  去11区
H.U.E., set a course. Sector 11.
不可以！我们还要修补那个缺口呢！
Out of the question! We've got a breach to close!
- HUE  11区  马上！ - 退后！
- H.U.E., Sector 11. Now! - Stand back.
- 啊！ - 我明白了  他是你儿子
- Ah! - I get it. He's your son.
但如果我们不去修补缺口  就可能引发世界末日了
But a world can end if we don't close the breach.
你说对了  这是我的儿子
You're right. It is my son.
- 我们非得去救他不可   - 天啦噜！你们啥情况！
- And we're getting him. - Dude! What the freak?!
盖瑞  你选哪个？地球  还是他儿子？
Gary, which is it? Earth, or his son?
- 你必须选一个 - 别忘了  你答应过我
- You're going to have to choose. - Remember. You promised.
要有大事发生了！
It's going down!
要有...大事...发生了  你们哪！
It... is... going... downtown, y'all!
我考虑好了  我两个都要
I've thought on it... and I choose both.
不过首先  我们先要去救小卡多
But first, we need to save Little Cato.
给我坐这！
In the chair!
- 你的意思就是你儿子比全...  - 正是如此
- You're saying your son is worth the lives of ... - Yes.
- 有这个必要吗？ - KVN  看住了她
- Is this totally necessary? - KVN, watch her.
真不敢相信我那么信任你
I can't believe I trusted you.
我们两件事都会做
We're gonna do both jobs.
等着我们  我们会回来的
Hang tight. We'll be back.
你真的决定要一起来吗
You sure you want to do this?
99%可能这是一个陷阱
There's a 99% chance that this is a trap.
陷阱恰恰是让英雄们拿来试镜的
Traps are just open casting calls for heroes.
而且  你已经把奎恩绑好了
Plus, you already tied up Quinn,
已经没有回头路了
so there's no real rebound after that.
- 你真是个“好”伙计  - 我更喜欢你叫我“超级好”的伙计
- You're a good friend. - I would've gone with "great."
不过无论如何  我也接受“好”好了
But whatever. I'll take... good.
- 发生了啥？ - 我觉得我们快要抱起来了
- What is happening? - I think we're about to hug.
要抱吗？
Should we?
海妖正在用歌声诱使我们拥抱
The siren's call is beckoning us to embrace.
海妖（Siren）：希腊神话中的女妖怪，她们用歌声使水手失神，令航船触礁沉没。
- 所以我们听她的  - 嗯
- We shan't ignore her. - Mmm.
真他妈好啊
Hell, yeah.
谢了老兄  正需要这个
Thanks, bud. Needed that.
走  一起把你的小子救回来
Let's get your boy back.
Chookity!
月饼  我们需要超大一波后援
Mooncake, we're gonna need rich sacks of back up.
Ooh!
我们要直捣总司令的流放地
We're goin' down to the Lord Commander's prison colony.
超危险哟！
It's dangerous!
Ooh!
这次行动会有生命威胁！我们说不定会死翘翘喔
It's life-threatening! We're probably gonna die.
准备好一起来了吗  小家伙？
I ... You got my back, little buddy?
Chookity!
我真不会卖安利  是不是
I didn't really sell that very well, did I?
狗带  这下没后援了
Crap! So no back up.
- 只有两个心怀梦想的男子汉  - HUE  我们来吧
- Just two hombres with a dream. - H.U.E., let's do this.
我们到了
We have arrived.
那就降落吧
Then land this thing.
很不幸  一旦降落  我们就会被发现
Unfortunately, if we land, we will be detected.
泽塔克隆  阿尔法
总司令流放地
你们需要空降
You'll have to space vault.
你是说  你是说我们要跳下去吗？
Are you sa... are you saying we gotta jump?
冲着那一坨紫云飞流直下几万米？
Jump like freakin' a zillion feet through that purple cloud?!
你能把我们送到多低？
How close can you get us?
嗯  送不到多低
Hmm. Nowhere near close enough.
我也没法从这么高跳下去  加把劲  HUE！
I can do nowhere near close enough. Punch it, H.U.E.!
这是啥？两个星球？！
What is this? Two planets?!
这有两个！去哪个？
There's two! Which one is it?
- 左边那个   - 右边的？
- It's left. - Right?
右边？音乐声太大了  我听不清！
R-Right? I-I can't hear you over the music!
- 那就右边了！   - 盖瑞！
- Right it is! - Gary!
哪里怪怪的
Something feels wrong.
是啊  因为我们来错地了
Yeah, because we're on the wrong planet.
同意  这个星球完全乱套了
Agreed. This planet is all wrong.
不  我说真的！咱们降到另一个星球了！
No, literally! We landed on the wrong planet!
老天爷啊！去他喵的！
Gosh dang it. Crap it rough!
当然咯  是左边那个  永远都被遗落的
Of course, it's left. It's always left.
Left：双关语，既指“左边”，又指“遗落”。
我生命里的所有东西都被遗落了  被遗落了！被遗落了！
Everything in my life has always been left. Left! Left!
呣  呣  呣  呣  嗯  喔  喔  喔
Yum, yum, yum, yum! Hmm. Wup, wup, wup!
喔  喔  喔
Wup, wup, wup!
KVN  长得那么火辣
How does it feel, KVN?
那么好看  那么帅
To be so hot, so good looking,
到底是怎样一种体验？
so... so handsome?
呃  所以我是银河一号上
Hmm. So, uh, am I the best-looking thing
- 最好看的东西？   - 目前来看是的
- aboard the Galaxy One? - By far.
哦哦哦哦哦
Ohhhhh.
奎恩  我能让你非常高兴
Quinn, I can make you very happy here.
- 我应该把盖瑞杀了吗？   - 啥？！不要
- Uh, should I kill Gary? - What?! No.
不过也快了  到时候就只有我们俩了
But soon. Then it will just be the two of us.
我只说了“火辣”  这不过是
And when I say hot, that doesn't even begin to describe
- 你将要体验到的东西的冰山一角呢   - 哦哦哦  我火辣辣地喜欢这个！
- what you've got coming. - Oooooh, I like it hot!
那你就... 快把我放出来吧  KVN
Then you... just... untie me, KVN.
也许过会我再把你绑回来？用真爱结绑你？
Maybe I can re-tie you later? With love knots?
真爱结（love knot）：又名“true lover's knot”，一种绳结的系法。
我到时候就可以把盖瑞杀了  对吧？
And then I can kill Gary later, right?
赶紧把我放出来  你个金属智障！
Just untie me, you metallic moron!
抱歉  确认一下  你说的是
Sorry, just to be clear, did you say
- 杀盖瑞  还是不杀盖瑞？  - 闭嘴！
- kill Gary, or don't kill Gary? - Shut up.
HUE  准备一架鹰式战机  我要去补个缺口
H.U.E., ready a HAWK. I got a breach to close.
奎恩  你应该再想想
Quinn, you should reconsider.
太迟了  把吊架打开
Too late. Open the hangar.
奎恩  在你走之前  我觉得你该看看这个
Quinn, I think there is something you should see before you go.
HUE  我毫无兴趣  我再也不相信任何人了
Not interested, H.U.E. No one left to trust.
你可以相信盖瑞
You can trust Gary.
你在开玩笑吧？
That's a joke, right?
这是什么？
What's this?
是时候让你了解真正的盖瑞了
It's time you get to know the real Gary.
这有成百上千条
There are hundreds.
是的  他服刑的每一天都录了一条
Yes, one for every day of his sentence.
Oooh.
嗨  奎恩  是我  盖瑞
Hey, Quinn! It's me, Gary.
刑期第一天！
Day one!
呃  我其实应该先给你道个歉
Uh, I should probably start by apologizing to you
当然了  还有桑切斯一家
and of course the Sanchez family
我把他们相当一般的饭馆炸飞了
for blowing up their very mediocre restaurant.
实话实说
If we're being honest.
我们面前摆放着一个“来错星球症”的病例
Looks like we've come down with a case of wrong-planet-itis.
- 不过很幸运  有办法治好它   - 什么？
- Luckily, there's a cure. - What?
跳到那边去！
Jump to the next planet!
啥？没背景音乐吗 宝贝？！
What? No tunes, baby?!
喔！
Whoo!
耶！我们在星际跳跃诶！
Yeah! We're planet jumping, man!
星际跳跃！
We are planet jumping!
好的！让我们把他们杀光吧！
All right! Let's kill them all!
他们看不见我们过来的！
They're never gonna see us coming!
哦！呜啊！
Oh! Whoa!
要我说  我们冲进去  开足火力
I say we burst in, guns blazing.
- 用火力晃瞎他们   - 为了小卡多
- Blind fire from the hip. - For Little Cato.
- 为了小卡多   - 喵！
- For Little Cato. - Meow!
噢  我的天哪
Oh, come on!
- 不错  周围没人   - 这妥妥的是个陷阱
- Oh, great. Nobody's around. - This is totally a trap.
- 你去哪？   - 去办点私事
- Where are you going? - I gotta take care of some biz.
- 好奇吗？   - 才不   - 我还以为你会好奇呢
- Curious?   - No.   - Thought so.
我要撒一泡大的
I gotta release a fat pee stream.
- 我不好奇   - 你绝对很好奇
- I wasn't curious. - You were totally curious.
- 我才没有！   - 我... 算了吧！
- No, I wasn't! - I ... Whatever!
- 爸爸   - 小卡多
- Papa. - Cato....
爸爸
Papa.
- 爸爸   - 小卡多！
- Papa. - Little Cato!
哦  呃  无意破坏团圆氛围
Ooh. Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, not to kill the reunion vibe,
不过你儿子似乎非常不对劲
but there's something mega not right with your boy.
是我的错  他生我气了
It's my fault. He's angry with me.
呃  好吧  你懂的  那就好  那就好
Well, it's, uh, you know, that's great. It's good, it's good.
但是  呃  他生气的方式太奇怪了
But, uh, he's got a weird way of showing that,
他已经气到双脚离地了！
in the fact that he's hovering off the ground!
- 嗯  你说的很有道理   - 很有道理？我就知道
- Yeah, you got a point. - I got a point? I know I do.
- 啊！   - 啊！啊！
- Aah! - Aah! Agh!
好吧 很高兴见到你  你叫什么名字？
Okay, nice to meet you. And your name is?
死比生甜
Death is sweeter than life.
我不懂为什么没有更多小孩叫这个名字
I don't know why more kids aren't named
“死比生甜”  你儿子真棒
"Death is sweeter than life." Fine boy you have here.
要来真的了  盖瑞  你要守信
Things are about to get real. You kept your promise, Gary.
回去吧  去找奎恩
Go back. Go back to Quinn.
你究竟为什么要这么说？
Why would you even say that?
因为... 你对我了解多少？
Because ... what do you really know about me?
我对你的了解就是  你说你不是猫
I know for a guy who says he's not a cat,
当然了  你很喜欢牛奶  除此以外就没什么了解了
you sure do love milk. Other than that, not a lot.
盖瑞  我恨总司令是有理由的
Gary, I hate the Lord Commander for a reason.
我曾经是他的二把手
I used to be his Second in Command.
我是杀戮大师
I was a master of death.
我会完成总司令让我做的所有事
I did anything the Lord Commander asked of me.
他对忠诚度的需求远超所有人
He above all else demanded loyalty.
某天  他召来他所有的将领
And one day, he ordered all of his generals
让他们杀死他们的头生子  以示忠诚
to prove their allegiance to him by killing their firstborn.
哦  这太阴暗了  像半夜一样暗
Oh, that's pretty dark. Like midnight dark.
简直是阴暗中的阴暗  超级超级阴暗
Like the darkest of the dark. Like super dark.
为了永恒！
For eternity!
为了总司令！
For the Lord Commander!
动手吧  阿瓦卡多  然后成为我的一把手
Do it, Avocato, and become my First.
动手！
Do it!
啊！
Aah!
- 你咋不把那厮给杀了？   - 我试过了
- Why didn't you just kill the Big Cheese? - I tried.
- 你试过？   - 是的
- Did you? - Yes.
好吧  我喜欢你这一点  我相信你
Okay, I like that out of you. Yeah, I believe you.
如果我再从你眼里看出迟疑  记好了
If I sense doubt in you ever again, remember ...
你儿子在我手里！
I own your son!
现在... 你也在我手里！
And now... I own you!
你一开始怎么和那个又小又绿的
How'd ya end up with a little green tic-tac
- 寰宇头号白痴扯上关系的？
- cosmic butt head like that in the first place?
- 别问我这种我都不想知道答案的问题   - 嗯
- By not asking the questions I didn't want to hear the answers to. - Mm-hmm.
- 这到底是什么意思？   - 我犯过很多错
- What the hell does that even mean? - I've made a lot of mistakes.
你还想和我扯上干系吗？
You still want anything to do with me?
所有人都犯过很多错  重要的是为了弥补过错
All of us are broken. Just a question of how much
你愿意走多远  付出多少东西
and how far we're willing to go to fix it.
看起来你很想弥补这个
Seems like you want that pretty bad.
- 是的   - 那么在我看来
- Yeah. - Then as far as I'm concerned,
我们回到原点了
we're back to where we started.
我答应过你要把你儿子救出来
I made you a promise to get your son back.
直到救出他之前  我都会协助你
And until we get him back, I got your back.
一个接着一个
It's back to back for life!
嗨哎哎哎哎  奎恩！
Heeeeeeey, Quinn!
依旧是盖瑞  我写了个打油诗
Gary again. I wrote a jingle ...
更像是抒情诗...  我叫它“爱的痛苦”
well, more of a ballad ... which I called "Love Pain."
事实上  等一下  不  它叫“痛苦的爱”
Actually, wait. No. It's called "Pain Love."
- 总之是这两个里的某一个   - 哦  一首歌？哦
- It's one of those two. - Ooh. A song? Ooh.
HUE 不给我吉他
H.U.E. won't let me have a guitar.
你真的觉得我会用吉他弦上吊自杀吗？！
Do you really think I'm going to hang myself by guitar strings?!
是的  老兄
Yes, dude.
好吧  你大概是猜对了
Yeah, well, you're probably right.
所以我用塑料勺子做了一个
So I made one out of a plastic spoon,
三条胶带  一根奇多  还有我的头发
three pieces of gravity tape, a Cheeto, and my hair.
好的  让我调个音
All right, let me just tune it.
其实我没太练过
You know, I haven't practiced this,
- 所以有点手生   - 那个呆子
- so I'm a little bit rusty. - That idiot.
♪ 疼痛如它  炽热如它 ♪
♪ It hurts, it burns ♪
♪ 痛苦如它  欢笑如它 ♪
♪ It pains, it laughs ♪
准备好了吗  爸爸
Ready, Papa?
准备好了  儿子
Ready, son.
我想说  你知道总司令
I mean, you know the Lord Commander's
- 就在这扇门后面吧？  - 惊喜一下！
- gonna be behind this door, right? - Surprise!
- 惊喜？你在开玩笑吧   - 老兄  没人会被你吓到
- Surprise? You gotta be kidding. - Dude, no one's surprised.
我可花了好长时间筹划这个呢！
I spent many hours of my day planning this!
为了制作这个惊喜  监狱里的其他人都被杀光了！
Everyone in the entire prison was murdered for this surprise!
呃  我不知道能和你说什么
Well, I don't know what to tell ya.
- 我觉得这样做不值得   - 闭嘴！
- I don't think it was worth it. - Silence!
好... 好的
O-Okay.
哦  哦哦哦
Oh. Ohhhh.
- 我还有惊喜等着你呢  那个盖瑞   - 我就叫盖瑞
- I have more surprises for you, the Gary. - Just... Gary.
至于你的父亲... 杀了他
As for your father... kill him.
啊啊啊啊啊
Ahhhhh!
来啊动手啊  你个矮子恶魔
Get on with it, you fun-sized devil.
我们都知道你不会告诉我月饼在哪的
We both know you won't tell me where Mooncake is,
所以我觉得  是时候自己动手找它了
so I think it's time I find him myself.
你在干啥？从我脑子里滚出去
What are you doin'? Get outta my mind, yo.
这个感官象限只有内部成员才能进来
This consciousness quadrant is members only.
快滚出去
So get out of my mind.
你不能这样  这是我的脑子
You can't do that. It's my mind.
我没邀请你进我的脑子
I didn't invite you into my mind.
快从我脑子里滚出去！
Get outta my mind!
这个闪光是什么意思？
What's this blinking one?
你有一封新消息
That means incoming message.
一定是刚刚的干扰让传送延迟了
It must have been delayed by the interference.
无论如何  把它放出来
Sure, whatever. Play it.
这可能是最后一次和你一对一说话了
This may be the last time we talk one-on-one.
我刚和阿瓦卡多说我要撒一泡大的
Uh, I told Avocato I was taking a fat pee,
但其实我是想和你最后说句话
but I just wanted to connect with you one last time
以防我死翘了之类的
in case, you know, I don't survive this.
奎恩  我知道我有一半时间都不会说话
Quinn, I know I don't say the right thing half the time
或者说任何时候都不会说话  实际上我有坏语症
or any of the time. You know, in fact, I have Word-arrhea.
就是一堆令人不快的话从我嘴里喷薄而出
It's an unpleasant spraying of words that just won't quit.
这是... 这真的是一种病
It ... I mean, it's ... it's a thing.
我想让你知道  我明白我伤害了你
Uh, I want you to know that I know that I hurt you back there.
- 安静  安静！   - 安静！
- Shut up. Shut up! - Shut up!
你能安静吗？！安静！
Could you please shut up?! Shut up!
我并不觉得那条绳子能把你绑太久
I don't expect that rope to hold you very long.
你很厉害  很机敏  很性感
I mean, you're pretty awesome and agile and hot.
我猜你现在已经从银河一号上跑出来了
I guess you probably left the Galaxy One by now.
但我只是想告诉你
But I want you to know that...
我本应该和你一起走到最后的
I would have went with you till the very end.
对不起 奎恩
I'm sorry, Quinn.
希望有朝一日  我能修复被我破坏的信任
I hope one day I can repair the trust I broke.
盖瑞总是把别人的生命放在第一位
Gary always puts other people's lives before his own.
HUE 盖瑞在哪？
H.U.E., where's Gary?
未知
Unclear.
我和他失去联系了
I have lost communications with him.
我们最好下去找他
Then we better get down there and find him.
我们来了 盖瑞
We're coming, Gary.
太他妈棒了  伙计
Hell, yeah, dawg.
INSIDE THE EPISODE AFTER CREDITS
啊
Aah!
小卡多
Little Cato?!
小卡多再也无法控制这个身体了
Little Cato no longer controls this body.
我知道你在里面  儿子
I know you're in there, son.
- 非也   - 啊！
- Wrong. - Agh!
我知道我是个失败的父亲
I've been a terrible father.
总司令毁了我  我也失去了你
The Lord Commander ruined me, and I lost you.
求求你了  儿子  不要让他把你也给毁了
Please, son. Don't let him ruin you.
万一太晚了呢？
What if it's too late?
不会的  你还在这
It's not. You're still right here.
爸爸？
Dad?
哦！
Ohh!
你怎么这么久才来？！
What the heck took you so long?!
现在我们快点出去
Now, let's get the hell out of here.
- 你在这啊   - 啊！
- There you are. - Aah!
月饼在银河一号上
Mooncake is aboard the Galaxy One.
不  他就在这
No. He's right here.
就是现在  月饼！
- Now, Mooncake! - Chookity!
不要！
No!
- 该走了  伙计！   - 顺便一提  我叫盖瑞
- Time to go, bud! - Name's Gary by the way.
很高兴看见你的爪子又着地了
Nice to see your paws touching the ground.
我也是  我叫小卡多
Little Cato. Likewise.
我们要回到银河一号上
We need to get to the Galaxy One.
我能做到
I got this.
- 嘣！好了   - 你小子快赶上我了
- Boom! Done. - You're almost as good as me.
切  我几年前就比你厉害了
Please, I passed you years ago.
啥？
Huh?
哦  来吧！啊！
Oh, come on! Aah!
KVN 来拯救地球了！
KVN is here to save the daaaay!
- 刚刚好险   - 我们快跑吧
- That was tight. - Let's move it.
- 盖瑞！   - 奎恩  你在哪？！
- Gary! - Quinn! Where are you?!
就是现在 HUE！
Now, H.U.E.!
KVN  我要把链子放下去了
KVN, I'm lowering the tether.
- 哦奎恩  你是真的爱我   - 我不爱你
- Oh, Quinn, you really do love me. - I don't love you.
- 我... 爱你！   - 万岁！
- I... love you. - Yes!
Hoo! Wah-wah-wah wah, wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah.
耶！盖瑞  盖瑞  盖瑞  嘿  嘿  嘿
Yay! Gary, Gary, Gary. Hey, hey, hey.
今天我如此激动
As excited as I am about today,
- 今后  将会有更多令我激动的事等着我   - 是啊
- I'm even more excited for tomorrow. - Yeah.
不！
No!
- 不要！   - 帮我照顾好我儿子！
- No. - Take care of my boy.
- 不！爸！
No! D-Dad!
♪ Welcome ♪
♪ 欢迎  欢迎 ♪
♪ Inch'Allah, Inch'Allah ♪
♪ 如神所愿  如神所愿 ♪
♪ Enter one ♪
♪ 我们将得以进入 ♪
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ 奇异的恩典 ♪
♪ Is pouring down ♪
♪ 自高天倾落 ♪
♪ Fear not this light ♪
♪ 不要怕这圣光 ♪
♪ We are of this light divine ♪
♪ 我们就在光明神之下 ♪
♪ So come ♪
♪ 所以来吧 ♪
♪ We move as one ♪
♪ 我们合为一体 ♪
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ 奇异的恩典 ♪
♪ is pouring down ♪
♪ 自高天倾落 ♪
♪ Fear not this light ♪
♪ 不要怕这圣光 ♪
♪ We are on this light divine ♪
♪ 我们就在光明神之下 ♪
♪ Welcome, enter one ♪
♪ 欢迎  来吧 ♪
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
幕后专访
INSIDE THE EPISODE
我觉得我们一直想给盖瑞一些
I think it was always... Gary... to make him
补偿性的特质  让他不是彻头彻尾的白痴
have some redeeming quality that he's not a complete idot.
至于总司令  他会做
The Lord Commander, he's going do
他力所能及的所有事  只为了能活下去
everything in his power to make sure he stays alive.
我们想做一些其它节目
We wanna to kind of do something that a show,
其它动画节目没做过的东西
an animated show really hasn't done before.
这是这个节目里非常精彩的一幕  真的是绝美的瞬间
It's an awesome moment of the show... really a beautiful moment.
父亲从炸弹威胁中救出儿子
The dad saving his son, from a bomb,
而这枚炸弹恰恰是总司令放在他背上的
that the Lord Commander put on his back.